Susanta Gayen

FRONT-END DEVELOPER.
BUDDINGPROGRAMMER

susantagayen4568@gmail.com

+91 9064901306

Kharagpur, West Bengal 👂

https://www.linkedin.com/in/susanta46 in

SUMMARY

A progressive person who wants to bring your company a good position. Applying the experience of good programming skills and understanding of the market to become a good programmer, bringing more value to Company. I strongly believe that i can be a perfect programmer of your company.

SKILLS

Programming Familiarity with languages: HTML, multiple

CSS, JavaScript. programming languages.

Python

programming skills. M.S. Word,

PowerPoint.

Good time

management and organisation skills.

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Appofix

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Making website with the using of Html, CSS, JavaScript.

Programmer

Code-a-Thon

Apr 2022 - May 2022

Code-a-Thon is a coding event of our college. Where students can participate and share the innovative ideas to others.

Where me and my team built a website.

Which was a doctor appointment based website. Where patients can take doctor's appointment sitting at home.

EDUCATION

BTech, Computer Science And Engineering

Coochbehar Goverment Engineering College [Koch Bihar, West Bengal] Aug 2021 - Present

Secondary & Higher Secondary Education

Jalchak Nateswari Netaji Vidyayatan [Jalchak, West Bengal]

Mar 2013 - Jun 2021

Class X [WBBSE] With 88.18% marks, 2019. Class XII [WBCHSE] with 74.20% marks, 2021.

LANGUAGES

English. Hindi.

Bengali.

HOBBIES

Playing Chess & Cricket.